SERGIO SALAZAR

FRONT-END DEVELOPER, IT ENGINEER

CONTACT



Address 10777 University Dr Surrey, BC - V3T 0E6



Phone +1 236 512 5551



Info github.com/seansabe/ linkedin.com/in/seansabe/

sasb1989@gmail.com

SKILLS

WEB AND MOBILE DEVELOPMENT (FRONT-END)

HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Angular, Svelte, Flutter.

SOFTWARE DESIGN

UI/UX design, software architecture, agile development, versioning.

OTHERS SKILLS

SQL Java, Scikit-learn, OpenCV, Scikit-image, Packet Tracer, C#, Python, PHP.

LANGUAGES

SPANISH

ENGLISH

SUMMARY

Professional in Systems Engineering with experience in Computer Systems, Software, Web and Mobile design and development. I have worked in front-end roles for more than three years leading UX/UI design/development, software integration, maintenance and testing tasks and activities for different proyects such as e-commerce webs, corporation-oriented webs and mobile applications.

EXPERIENCE

2022 - Present

Douglas College

CODING INSTRUCTOR

Planned, organized, directed computer-related, digital art and coding camps for 8-13 years old kids.

2021 - 2022

Faimedia

WEB DEVELOPER

Developed, wrote, modified, integrated and tested Web site related code and Web application interfaces.

Monitored and maintained web sites functionality.

2018 - 2022

Reactive Source S.A.S

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (FRONT)

Designed, wrote, modified, integrated and tested software code for e-commerce, Internet and mobile applications (Front-end oriented).

Tested and analyzed data to monitor quality, security, user interface experiences and areas of improvement.

Participated in web site architecture and design in collaboration with designers or clients.

EDUCATION

2022 - Present

Douglas College COMPUTER & INFORMATION EMERGING TECH PBD

New Westminster, BC

2017 - 2020

Universidad del Valle

MASTER IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING - COMPUTER VISION

Cali, Valle del Cauca, Colombia.

2014 - 2016

Universidad Nacional Abierta y a Distancia UNAD SYSTEMS ENGINEERING

Palmira, Valle del Cauca, Colombia.